Guide to the Turkish Photography Collection 1910-1990 AD.MC.007
AbuDhabi
- Three females in coats seated in high grass in the countryside. The roof of a house can be seen in the background. 8.8 x 14.0 cm, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  Coats; Gardens; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Women
- A class photo of young males with an older adult male seated in the front row. All looking to the left away from camera. 8.4 x 13.1 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  Boys; Education; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Schools; Suits
- A seated older woman with a baby on her lap and a second woman standing behind them, a stroller is in the foreground. Ottoman writong on the back. 9.0 x 13.8 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  Children; Family; Gardens; Ottoman Writing; Photographic Prints; Women
- Four men seated at a table smoking nargile (shisha). 8.7 x 14.0 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  Eating; Group Portraits; Men; Nargile; Photographic Prints; Samovar; Smoking; Tea
- A bride and groom, with flower arrangements. Photo is badly damaged. 13.1 x 8.3 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  Couple; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Wedding Portraits
- A young couple with a baby on their lap. Studio Sunar, Yedikule, Istanbul, Turkey. 13.4 x 8.5 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  Family Portraits; Istanbul, Turkey; Jewelry; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography
- A young couple, woman is wearing a dark colored dress with a white collar. Foto S. Sureyya, Istanbul. Turkish writing on the front. 13.7 x 8.1 cm, 14 October 1935 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  Bow Tie; Couple; Foto S. Sureyya; Istanbul, Turkey; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Turkish Writing
- A young female standing in a black dress, holding a light colored purse. 13.7 x 8.5 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  Fashion Accessories; Individual Portrait; Jewelry; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Women
- An older child in a checkered suit with large white shirt collar, holding a small baby on a chair. Turkish writing on the back. 13.7 x 8.8 cm, 17 January 1934 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  Children; Family Portraits; Furnishings; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Turkish Writing
- A woman in a light colored dress with a dark colored collar, a pearl necklace. Ottoman writing on the back. 13.8 x 8.5 cm, 18 May 1934 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  Furnishings; Individual Portrait; Jewelry; Ottoman Writing; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Women
- Two young females standing holding a small boy with a white hat. Foto Marmara, Istanbul, Turkey. 13.6 x 8.7 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  Boys; Children; Family Portraits; Foto Marmara; Girls; Hats; Istanbul, Turkey; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography
- A group young males in suits and ties/bow ties, ornate curtains in the background. 8.9 x 14.0 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  Bow Tie; Group Portraits; Men; Photographic Prints; Suits
- Five young females embracing in front of a building with a tree in the foreground. 8.9 x 13.9 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Trees; Women
- Female students with older female seated in the middle. Foto Sen, Istanbul, Turkey. 8.5 x 13.3 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Education; Girls; Group Portraits; Istanbul, Turkey; Photographic Prints; Students; Studio Photography; Women
- A family group, a young girl in a white dress holding flowers, in between four adults. 13.8 x 8.7 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Family Portraits; Flowers; Girls; Hats; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography
- A young children with paper crowns on their heads. 14.0 x 9.0 cm, 3 May 1967 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Boys; Ceremony; Children; Education; Flags; Party; Photographic Prints
- Males seated around wooden tables outside in a garden/woods. 8.8 x 13.8 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Boys; Drinking; Gardens; Group Portraits; Men; Photographic Prints
- An older man in a suit holding a young female in dark dress on a fence in front of a castle and water. 14.0 x 9.0 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Archaeological Sites; Architecture; Family; Photographic Prints; Seas
- Three males fighting, boy in a shoulder lock has his hand raised. Turkish writing on the back. 8.5 x 13.9 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Boys; Education; Performance Play; Photographic Prints; Turkish Writing
- Young females standing at a wooden stair case on a cobbled courtyard. Ottoman writing on the back. 8.7 x 13.3 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Architecture; Girls; Group Portraits; Ottoman Writing; Photographic Prints; Uniforms; Women
- Four young females wearing dark winter coats. Ottoman writing on the back. 13.5 x 8.1 cm, 2 [-?-] 1928 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Coats; Girls; Ottoman Writing; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Women
- Adult males and females seated around a dinner table singing along with a man playing saz, a traditional string instrument with a long neck. 8.5 x 12.4 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Drinking; Eating; Men; Music; Musical Instruments; Photographic Prints; Smoking; Women
- A young male wearing a fez. 13.9 x 8.7 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Boys; Children; Fez; Individual Portrait; Maritime Outfit; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography
- A female in a dark dress with pearls on her neck and in her hair, holding a book. 13.8 x 8.8 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  Books; Individual Portrait; Jewelry; Ottoman Writing; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Women
- A male in traditional Turkish clothes, with a big black mustache. Turkish writing on the back. 13.8 x 8.8 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  Fez; Furnishings; Men; Mustaches; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Traditional Dress; Turkish Writing
- A female in a dark dress with a big bow in her hair, holding a small lighter purse. Ottoman writing on the back. 14.0 x 8.8 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  Fashion Accessories; Furnishings; Individual Portrait; Ottoman Writing; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Women
- An Armenian family seated at an outdoor table with two hats on the table. Armenian writing on the reverse. 9.0 x 14.0 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  Armenian Writing; Drinking; Family Portraits; Hats; Photographic Prints; Restaurants
- Three young females, two with updos and one with a bob. 8.3 x 12.6 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  Makeup; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Women
- A young couple, female is wearing pearl earrings and a flowery scarf. Studio Hulya. 12.9 x 8.7 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  Couple; Jewelry; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Suits
- Two young females in a garden, one seated on a bench reading. 14.0 x 9.0 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  Books; Gardens; Photographic Prints; Reading; Women
- A family group, covered female, adult male in suit with prayer beads in left hand. Foto Baradan, Izmir, Turkey. 13.9 x 9.0 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  Family Portraits; Foto Baradan; Head Covers; Izmir, Turkey; Photographic Prints; Rosary; Studio Photography
- A female in a patterned skirt suit with updo and two children. 13.7 x 8.2 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  Children; Family Portraits; Gardens; Photographic Prints; Suits
- A family group, various young female and male children. One boy holds a newspaper. 13.6 x 8.6 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  Children; Countryside; Family Portraits; Newspapers
- A young female child in a patterned dress, holding a watering can. Turkish writing on the reverse. 13.5 x 8.4 cm, 23 April 1945 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  Children; Girls; Individual Portrait; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography
- A young female child with a light patterned dress and multiple bows in her hair. Turkish writing on the reverse. 13.5 x 8.5 cm, 18 June 1950 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  Children; Girls; Individual Portrait; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Turkish Writing
- A young couple standing on a checkered floor, female is covered with a light scarf. Foto M. Ipek, Odemis, Turkey. 13.7 x 8.7 cm, 28 December 1953 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  Couple; Head Covers; Odemis, Turkey; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography
- A bride and groom and two young females. Yesim, Aksaray, Istanbul, Turkey. Turkish writing on the back. 14.0 x 9.2 cm, 12 May 1978 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  Brides; Grooms; Istanbul, Turkey; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Turkish Writing; Wedding Portraits
- A young couple, female in light colored dress is holding a bouquet of flowers. Turkish writing on the back. 13.5 x 8.5 cm, 10 October 1942 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  Ankara, Turkey; Couple; Flowers; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Turkish Writing
- A group hiking on a mountain. One adult male has binocular. Writing on the back. Ober-Schreiberhau, Germany (after WWII, became part of Poland). 8.9 x 11.7 cm, 7 October 1944 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  Children; German Writing; Germany; Girls; Hiking; Men; Nature; Photographic Prints; Women
- A family group standing outside a wooden house with barred windows. 13.8 x 8.9 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  Architecture; Children; Family; Photographic Prints
- A seated male in a dark suit holding a hat and a cane in his hand. Writing on the front. 14.0 x 9.0 cm, 15 June 1931 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  Fashion Accessories; Hats; Individual Portrait; Men; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Suits
- Young adults in the countryside, a young female in plaid dressed squatting on the far right. 9.0 x 13.0 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  Countryside; Group Portraits; Men; Photographic Prints; Women
- A family group with trees in the background. Turkish writing on the back. 8.6 x 13.4 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  Family Portraits; Gardens; Photographic Prints; Turkish Writing
- A group of men standing at a train station in military uniform with a train in the background. 8.5 x 11.7 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  Group Portraits; Men; Military; Photographic Prints; Soldiers; Trains; Uniforms
- A soldier drinking from a canteen in dark military uniform. Turkish writing on the back. 13.9 x 8.8 cm, 4 May 1941 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  Drinking; Individual Portrait; Military; Photographic Prints; Soldiers; Turkish Writing; Uniforms
- Three women in the same uniform at Garanti Bank around a desk with a telephone on it. Studyo Nuri. 8.9 x 13.9 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  Banks; Istanbul, Turkey; Makeup; Photographic Prints; Uniforms; Women
- A couple sitting in fornt of a desk, man is wearing winged-tipped shoes. Yildirim, Foto Kemal Mete, Inonu Cd. Istanbul, Turkey. 8.7 x 13.6 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  Flowers; Gatherings; Hats; Istanbul, Turkey; Men; Photographic Prints; Women
- Five adults, one seated male with arms crossed in lap and one male wears a hat. 13.6 x 8.6 cm, 5 March 1945 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  Family Portraits; Hats; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Suits
- Two males, one in military uniform standing in front of an Ataturk staue mounted on a horse. 12.0 x 9.0 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  Architecture; Ataturk; Men; Military; Photographic Prints; Soldiers; Statues; Uniforms
- A small family, young male is wearing a ruffled shirt with vest. Turkish writing on reverse. 8.9 x 13.5 cm, 16 September 1947 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  Family Portraits; Fashion Accessories; Makeup; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Suits; Turkish Writing
- A couple standing in front of some flower arrangements. Female is wearing a black dress with a white ruffled shirt and white bow on her head. 13.3 x 8.7 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  Ceremony; Coats; Couple; Fashion Accessories; Flowers; Photographic Prints
- A family group, two girls are wearing the same plaid dress with dark bows in their hair. Turkish writing on the back. Foto Sabah, Beyoglu, Istanbul, Turkey. 8.6 x 13.6 cm, 25 September 1944 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  Beyoglu, Istanbul, Turkey; Children; Family Portraits; Foto Sabah; Girls; Jewelry; Makeup; Photographic Prints
- Two males seated in wooden chairs outside a storefront. Ramiz Goksay, "Telefonu 7020", Izmir, Turkey. 8.9 x 13.9 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  Izmir, Turkey; Men; Photographic Prints; Shopkeepers
- A frowning young female in a light dress with light bow in her hair standing on a wicker chair. 13.5 x 8.6 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  Children; Furnishings; Girls; Individual Portrait; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography
- A young couple, male is in military uniform. Foto S. Sureyya, Istanbul, Turkey. 13.8 x 8.5 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  Coats; Couple; Foto S. Sureyya; Istanbul, Turkey; Military; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Uniforms
- A family group with three children sitting on a wicker chair. Foto Safak, Izmir, Turkey. Turkish writing on the reverse. 13.5 x 8.8 cm, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  Children; Family Portraits; Furnishings; Head Covers; Izmir, Turkey; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Turkish Writing
- A young female as "Japanese Girl" in a light silk dress with a oriental fan in her right hand. Turkish writing on reverse. 12.7 x 8.9 cm, 28 April 1962 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  Costumes; Education; Gatherings; Photographic Prints; Traditional Dress; Turkish Writing; Women
- A group of young females with one male seated in a dark Western suit. Foto Sabah, Beyoglu, Istanbul, Turkey. 8.9 x 13.9 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  Beyoglu, Istanbul, Turkey; Foto Sabah; Girls; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Suits; Wedding Ceremony; Women
- A young female looking up with dark lip stick. Foto-Ressam, Salah Uz, Beyoglu, Turkey. Turkish writing on the reverse. 13.4 x 8.5 cm, 28 March 1937 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  Beyoglu, Istanbul, Turkey; Individual Portrait; Makeup; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Turkish Writing; Women
- A family, seated female with covered head holds a young child in white. 13.7 x 8.7 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  Children; Family; Furnishings; Head Covers; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Suits
- Two male seated in suits with two young males and a baby. 13.9 x 8.8 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  Boys; Children; Eye Glasses & Sunglasses; Family; Photographic Prints; Suits
- A young female in a green outfit and red lip stick. Foto Opera. Turkish writing on the reverse. 13.6 x 8.7 cm, 12 March 1957 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  Handtinting; Individual Portrait; Makeup; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Turkish Writing; Women
- A mixed group seated indoors, older female in the center in a striped dress. 8.4 x 13.8 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  Family; Men; Photographic Prints; Women
- A covered woman in a dark dress holding a baby dress in a white outfit. Foto Bayer (written in Turkish and Arabic). 13.7 x 8.4 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  Children; Family; Head Covers; Ottoman Writing; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Women
- A bride in a white dress with another young female in a light patterend dress standing in front of a mirror. 8.6 x 13.5 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  Brides; Jewelry; Makeup; Photographic Prints; Wedding Ceremony; Wedding Veil; Women
- A young couple, female on the left is wearing a floral patterened outfit. Foto Sabah, Beyoglu, Istanbul, Turkey. 8.6 x 13.7 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  Beyoglu, Istanbul, Turkey; Couple; Foto Sabah; Makeup; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography
- A mixed group on a boat on the water. 8.8 x 12.0 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  Boats; Eye Glasses & Sunglasses; Head Covers; Men; Photographic Prints; Seas; Women
- A young bride and groom, bride holding a bouquet of long white flowers, groom has a checkered pocket square. Foto Kenan Akgul, Uskudar, Turkey. 13.8 x 8.8 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  Brides; Flowers; Grooms; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Uskudar, Turkey; Wedding Portraits; Wedding Veil
- A seated bride with groom standing behind her and a curtain in the background. 13.0 x 8.5 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  Brides; Flowers; Grooms; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Wedding Portraits; Wedding Veil
- Three women, two on the left are wearing floral patterend outfits. Foto Ridvan. Turkish writing on the reverse. 8.5 x 13.6 cm, 12 January 1948 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  Family Portraits; Makeup; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Turkish Writing; Women
- A male with a mustache seated on a chair in a garden. 14.0 x 9.0 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  Gardens; Men; Mustaches; Photographic Prints
- A couple, male in a military hat with short mustache. Turkish writing on the back. 13.6 x 8.6 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  Coats; Couple; Fashion Accessories; Military; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Soldiers; Studio Photography; Turkish Writing; Uniforms
- A mixed group in the country side. 8.9 x 14.0 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  Countryside; Group Portraits; Men; Mountains; Photographic Prints; Women
- A mixed group standing in front of a war memorial, statue of soldier with arm raised in the background. 14.0 x 8.8 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  Group Portraits; Guns; Photographic Prints; Soldiers; Statues
- A young female in a dark dress with a white necklace and earings. Foto Galatasaray, Beyoglu, Istanbul, Turkey. 14.0 x 8.8 cm, 22 December 1956 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  Beyoglu, Istanbul, Turkey; Foto Galatasaray; Individual Portrait; Jewelry; Makeup; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Women
- A young family, female has flowers pinned to her dress, baby in white dress, male in light suit holding baby. Foto Sabah, Beyoglu, Istanbul, Turkey. 13.3 x 8.5 cm, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  Beyoglu, Istanbul, Turkey; Family Portraits; Flowers; Foto Sabah; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography
- A covered female, young standing female in dark dress and purse, young standing male in dark suit and round glasses. Foto Sen. 10.9 x 9.0 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  Eye Glasses & Sunglasses; Family Portraits; Fashion Accessories; Head Covers; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Suits
- A male in a military uniform with a lit cigarette in his left hand in the country side. 13.6 x 8.4 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  Cigarettes; Gardens; Military; Photographic Prints; Smoking; Soldiers; Uniforms
- A young family, male in dark suit with a lit cigarette, female with white head cover and dark dress, young male in a sailor outfit. Sebah & Joaillier, Pera, Cons/ple. 9.0 x 14.0 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  Constantinople; Family Portraits; Head Covers; Maritime Outfit; Ottoman Writing; Photographic Prints; Sebah & Joaillier, Constantinople; Smoking; Studio Photography
- A group of young males standing and two reclining with football. Ottoman writing on the back. 9.0 x 14.0 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  Architecture; Group Portraits; Men; Ottoman Writing; Photographic Prints; Sports
- A mixed group, seated and standing, with trees in the background. 13.4 x 8.3 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  Coats; Gardens; Hats; Head Covers; Men; Photographic Prints; Suits; Women
- Two females and a male with a cane in the country side. Ottoman writing on the front. 13.5 x 8.7 cm, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  Countryside; Family Portraits; Head Covers; Ottoman Writing; Photographic Prints
- A young couple, female in a light top with a bow. Foto Turan, Carsikapi, Turkey. Turkish writing on the reverse. 16-939 Kurban Bayrami (Eid Al Fitr). 8.7 x 13.3 cm, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  Clocks & Watches; Couple; Istanbul, Turkey; Jewelry; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Turkish Writing
- A group of males in miltary uniform in front of a car. Ottoman writing on the reverse. 8.7 x 13.8 cm, 8 March 1943 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  Cars; Men; Military; Ottoman Writing; Photographic Prints; Soldiers; Uniforms
- A mixed group in formal dress seated around a group of tables. Foto Rifat. 8.8 x 13.8 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  Furnishings; Gatherings; Jewelry; Makeup; Men; Photographic Prints; Women
- A bride and groom with members of their families around them. Turkish writing on the back. 8.5 x 13.4 cm, 15 June [-?-] (Box 1, Folder 13)
  Brides; Children; Grooms; Head Covers; Photographic Prints; Turkish Writing; Wedding Ceremony
- A group of mixed males and females seated a dinner table. Basin Foto Studio, Beyoglu, Istanbul, Turkey. Turkish writing on the back. 13.7 x 8.8 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  Beyoglu, Istanbul, Turkey; Drinking; Eating; Gatherings; Photographic Prints; Turkish Writing
- A young female in short dress and tan trench coat seated in a white chair. 12.5 x 8.0 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  Coats; Individual Portrait; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Women
- A young male in a dark suit and patterned pocket square. 11.5 x 8.7 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  Individual Portrait; Men; Mustaches; Painted Backdrops; Studio Photography; Suits
- A young male standing on a balcony in a light suit with a fedora. 8.8 x 13.9 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  Hats; Individual Portrait; Men; Photographic Prints
- A young couple standing in tall grass in the country side. 8.5 x 13.7 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  Couple; Gardens; Maritime Outfit; Photographic Prints
- Two young females in lederhosen. Studio Mustafa, Izmir. Turkish writing on back. 8.5 x 13.3 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  Children; Izmir, Turkey; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Traditional Dress
- A young couple on the dance floor, female in a pin stripped skirt suit. Turkish writing on the back "The best days of my life". 8.5 x 13.3 cm, 1 May 1941 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  Couple; Dancing; Photographic Prints; Turkish Writing
- Two women in bathing suits at the beach. 9.2 x 14.0 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  Bathing Suits; Beach; Hats; Photographic Prints; Women
- A woman in a black dress with a white flower on the front and black hat, standing in the door way of house. 13.9 x 9.0 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  Hats; Makeup; Photographic Prints; Women
- A woman in a black skirt and dark top seated on a chair in front a window sill with potted plants. 13.6 x 8.8 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  Furnishings; Photographic Prints; Potted Plants; Women
- A seated female in a light patterned dress. 14.0 x 8.8 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
- A female leaning on a plant stand, wearing a fur lined coat and a head cover. 13.8 x 8.5 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  Coats; Furnishings; Head Covers; Individual Portrait; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Women
- Two young males with mustaches with a potted flower on a table between them. 14.0 x 9.0 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  Furnishings; Men; Mustaches; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Potted Plants; Studio Photography; Suits
- Two females in long coats standing in front of a large tree in the country side. Pendik, Istanbul, Turkey. Turkish writing on the back. 13.8 x 8.8 cm, 12 March 1951 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  Architecture; Coats; Gardens; Istanbul, Turkey; Photographic Prints; Women
- A young female in a light silk dress with a dark colored purse in her lap. Ottoman writing on the back. 12.7 x 9.0 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  Architecture; Fashion Accessories; Ottoman Writing; Photographic Prints; Women
- A young female in a dark winter coat with a dark hat, three tufts of hair are hanging out of the hat. Ottoman writing on the back. 14.0 x 9.0 cm, 6 July 1921 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  Head Covers; Individual Portrait; Ottoman Writing; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Women
- Two males standing in front of some hedges and trees, one is a uniform holding a hat. Ottoman writing on the back. 13.8 x 8.4 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  Gardens; Men; Ottoman Writing; Photographic Prints; Suits; Uniforms
- A young female in a dark dress, background has some special effects. 13.7 x 8.5 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  Individual Portrait; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Women
- A group of females and males surrounding a bride. 13.9 x 9.0 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  Brides; Grooms; Jewelry; Makeup; Photographic Prints; Wedding Portraits; Women